

EDUARDO URIAN

CONTACT

+1 (647) 224-0121

EDUARDO.URIAN@GMAIL.COM

3187 PEARWOOD PLACE. MISSISSAUGA, ON

PROFILE

I am a Game Design student currently attending Brock University/Niagara College with a specialization in User Experience Design.

In the same way that User Experience Designers act as the bridge between the developer and the player/user, I would like to be the bridge that connects the consumer to the brand, applying my customer centric mindset to the services I provide.

EXPERIENCE

SALES ASSOCIATE

SKECHERS RETAIL | NOV 2019 - PRESENT

- Engage with customers and deliver exceptional customer service
- Use extensive product knowledge to recommend footwear and accessories that meet customer needs
- Maintain visual appearance of the store by managing store displays and merchandise layouts
- Guarantee accuracy and integrity when conducting customer transactions at cash wrap

TEA BARISTA

THE ALLEY | JUN 2019 - OCT 2019

- Welcomed customers, educated them on our products and services and answered any questions
- Learned about brewing methods, beverage blends and presentation techniques to maintain product quality
- Proficiently prepared blended and cold drinks
- Cleaned and restocked work stations, emptied garbage and sanitized equipment

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS, GAME DESIGN BROCK UNIVERSITY | 2017-PRESENT

ADVANCED DIPLOMA, GAME DEVELOPMENT NIAGARA COLLEGE | 2017-PRESENT

SOFT SKILLS

- Creative Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Oral Communication
- Adaptability

- Quick Learner
- Team-Oriented
- Detail-Oriented
- Customer Centric

ACHIEVEMENTS

NIAGARA COLLEGE GAME DEVELOPMENT LAUNCH SECOND YEAR PROJECT AWARD OF EXCELLENCE | 2019

• 1st Place Project Award for the best game created by a second-

year team

NIAGARA COLLEGE

PRESIDENT'S HONOUR ROLL | 2017

• Awarded for outstanding scholastic record, earning a term average of 90%+

FATHER MICHAEL GOETZ CATHOLIC SECONDARY SCHOOL HONOUR ROLL | 2013-2017

• Achieved an 80%+ average all throughout high school